Impartial Umpire Files 6057
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- U.S. Steel Corp. Board of Arbitration T300-1300. (Box 22)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. Board of Arbitration T - 300 - 499, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration T - 500 - 599, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration T 600- 799, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration T 800- 999, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration # T 1000-1300, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- U.S. Steel Miscellaneous Divisions & Arbitrations. (Box 23)
  - U.S. Steel - Carnegie- Illinois Board of Arbitration # CI 1 - 300, 1951-1953 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Steel Carnegie- Illinois Board of Con. And ARB. CI 1-149, 1945-1950 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Steel Carnegie - Illinois Board of Con. And ARB. CI 150-199, 1949-1952 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Steel - Carnegie- Illinois (South Works) Board of Arbitration, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. Columbia- Geneva Steel Div. Sub Arbitration Procedure Sub 1 - 100, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation - Consolidated Western Steel Div. Impartial Umpire Decisions No. CWU 1-50, 1957-1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Steel * Columbia Steel Company Board of Con. And ARB. Col - 1 - 199, 1946-1964 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. - Fairless Works Board of Arbitration, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. Geneva Plant Arbitration Award G- 1-199, 1948-1965 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - H-, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation - Homestead District Works Impartial Umpire Decisions No. P 1-100, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. - National Tube Division Board of Arbitration N- 1-199, 1945-1958 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. National Tube Division Board of Arbitration - Cases 400-599, 1962-1966 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Steel Co. Tennessee Coal & Iron Div. Board of Con. And ARB. T- 1 - 299, 1946-1955 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. * National Tube Division Board of Arbitration N-200 - 399, 1953-1961 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - United States Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration Grievances WS -, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Steel Industry Arbitrations - Crucible Steel- U.S. Steel Am. Wire & Steel Division. (Box 24)
  - Crucible Steel Company Umpire Decisions GA 1-50, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Inland Steel Company Arbitration Awards, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Kennecott Copper Corporation Opinions and Awards, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Maryland Shipbuilding & Drydock Co. and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipubuilding Workers of America, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Titanium Metals Corp. of America and United Steel Workers of America, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - U.S. President's Missile Sites and Labor Commission Decisions and Orders, 1961-1966 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Steel Am. Wire and Steel Company Board of Con. And ARB. A - 1 - 199, 1945-1947 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Steel - Am. Wire and Steel Company Board of Con. And ARB. A - 200- 549, 1948-1951 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Steel - Am Steel and Wire Company Board of Con. And ARB. 4-400- 550, 1951-1953 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Steel - Am. Wire and Steel Division Board of Arbitration- A- 499-750, 1953-1957 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. - Am. Steel & Wire Div. Arbitration Award A- 750-999, 1957-1963 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Steel- Am. Wire and Steel Co. Board of Con. And ARB. A-1000-2000, 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Misc., 1980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Joint Relations Board, 1934-1955 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Social Service Employee Union Grievances - Impartial Umpire Arbitrations, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Railroad Industry- Certain Carriers and Certain of their Employees, 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 16)